HEYVICVOSKOVSKY@GMAIL.COM *

VIC-VOSKOVSKY.GITHUB.IO * @COALESCENCEGG *

1+(224) 595-5517

ABOUT ME

Technical data scientist with approx. 5 yrs of experience solving complex business challenges and translating strategic thinking into actionable and analytical frameworks. Creative thinker with domain knowledge in several industries including e-commerce, social media, automotive and esports. Founder of Coalescence.gg, a tech and esports driven weekly newsletter, avid gamer and general believer that anything that can be measured, can be improved.

SKILLS

- Data analysis in code, spreadsheets & BI-tools.
- Visualizing data in Python, Excel, Tableau & more.
- Python
- BeautifulSoup NLP
- SQL
- Excel
- Seaborn

- Git
- Pandas
- Matplotlib

- HTML
- Keras
- Tensorflow

- Scala
- Tableau
- DOMO

- AWS
- Google Cloud Google Analytics

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DATA SCIENCE FELLOW

GENERALASSEMB.LY | CHICAGO. IL | MARCH 2020 - JUNE 2020

- Completed a 12-week, 450+ hour immersive Data Science course, advancing my knowledge of Data Science.
- Gained fundamental coding experience needed to use Python, Scala, HTML & SQL professionally.
- Completed & published 5 rigorous Data Science projects, which culminated with a final capstone project.
- Harnessed computer science techniques to solve regression, classification, NLP & Neural Network problems.
- Created a ranking algorithm for Riot Games League of Legends to analyze and predict 2020 Worlds Tournament.
- Predicted housing prices, performed hypothesis tests, systematically scraped the web & more.

FINANCIAL ANALYST - ACCOUNT MANAGEMENT

IAAI.COM | WESCHESTER, IL | OCT 2017 - NOV 2018

- Advised Berkshire-Hathaway account team on complex business decisions with over 500k vehicles sold annually.
- Assisted leadership on large CAT reporting initiatives in Tableau, using a database with 3m units sold per year.
- Supported national account managers in making concise financial decisions based on 15 years worth of data.
- Launched & administered reports on business metrics using Report Builder, Tableau & Excel.
- Lead all Tableau implementations, training and deployment projects to phase out Report Builder.

BUSINESS OPERATIONS & STRATEGY ANALYST - FIRST HIRE

KUNUNU.COM | BOSTON, MA | JUL 2016 - AUG 2017

- Implemented, launched and administered DOMO & Tableau using BI tools for company-wide consumption.
- Developed lead ranking algorithm to help parse large amount of leads for a team of 5 sales executives & CSO.
- Headed big data projects between Kununu and Monster.com, primarily containing 7m+ rows of customer data.
- Partnered with executives to create a robust sales funnel, answer questions & track KPI's for 3 departments.
- Created business materials used on sales calls & spearheaded several quality of life projects for sales dept.

BUSINESS ANALYST - FIRST HIRE

PRISMBRANDS.CO | CHICAGO, IL | APR 2013 - JUN 2016

- Designed and deployed Trackvia Cloud Database for managing over 1m units of inventory sold annually.
- Directed day to day warehouse & WeWork office operations while lowering costs and simplifying processes.
- Administrated various reporting projects for managing partner, launched profitability and inventory reports.
- Managed Shopify, Ebay & Amazon marketing campaigns to maximize sales and minimize spend.
- Pitched and secured big ecommerce partnership contract with a international manufacturer.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN FINANCE

DEPAUL UNIVERSITY, CHICAGO | GRADUATED - 2014